<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ARFC</title>
    <description>Website for the Advanced Reactors and Fuel Cycles group</description>
    <link>http://arfc.github.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://arfc.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2016 09:14:07 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2016 09:14:07 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Group Members Join ARFC</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;As the first semester of the ARFC group begins this fall, I’m excited to 
announce that a number of researchers will join the group.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alexander Lindsay will be joining us a postdoctoral scholar. He received his
undergraduate degree in Chemical Engineering from the University of Washington
and received his PhD this summer from North Carolina State University. He will
be joining ARFC as well as the &lt;a href=&quot;https://dxl.ncsa.illinois.edu/&quot;&gt;Data Exploration Laboratory
(DXL)&lt;/a&gt; led by Matthew Turk. His activities will
emphasize open source advanced reactor multiphysics and his collaboration with
DXL may advance visual exploration of simulation results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andrei Rykhlevskii will be joining the group as a PhD student. He has a degree
in Nuclear Engineering from Bauman Moscow State Technical University as well as
a Masters of Science in Finanace from the Financial University in Moscow. His
work will likely also emphasize open source advanced reactor multiphysics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additionally, a small team of undergraduate researchers will join the group 
this year.  These include Kathryn Mummah and Jin Whan Bae of NPRE as well as 
Matthew Worley and Yukun Tan who will join us through the &lt;a href=&quot;http://spin.ncsa.illinois.edu/&quot;&gt;NCSA 
SPIN&lt;/a&gt; program.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the help of all of these researchers, I expect ARFC will really be able to
hit the ground running.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2016 21:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://arfc.github.io/jekyll/update/2016/08/16/new-arfc-members/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://arfc.github.io/jekyll/update/2016/08/16/new-arfc-members/</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Huff Featured in NPRE News</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am thrilled to be featured in the NPRE news today. Susan Mumm wrote a lovely 
article announcing that I’ll be joining NPRE. You can read the article 
&lt;a href=&quot;http://npre.illinois.edu/news/reactor-physicist-katy-huff-joins-npre-faculty&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 21:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://arfc.github.io/jekyll/update/2016/07/12/huff-npre-article/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://arfc.github.io/jekyll/update/2016/07/12/huff-npre-article/</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>ARFC and ERGS Receive NEUP R&amp;D Award</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The United State Department of Energy &lt;a href=&quot;https://neup.inl.gov/Lists/Headlines/AnnouncementDispForm.aspx?ID=134&quot;&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt; today that ARFC, in collaboration with the University of South Carolina’s Energy and Resources Group led by Anthony Scopatz 
(&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ergs.sc.edu/&quot;&gt;ERGS&lt;/a&gt;), would recieve 3 years of NEUP R&amp;amp;D support. The 
ARFC group will be able to support extensive work on predictive deployment 
models for the Cyclus fuel cycle simulator and its library of available 
modules, Cycamore. The abstract for this award, 
“Demand Driven Cycamore Archetypes” can be 
found 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://neup.inl.gov/FY16%20Abstracts/Research%20and%20Development/CFA-16-10512_TechnicalAbstract_2016CFATechnicalAbstract10512.pdf&quot;&gt;online&lt;/a&gt;
alongside 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://neup.inl.gov/SitePages/FY16%20RandD%20Awards.aspx&quot;&gt;many other 2016 NEUP awards&lt;/a&gt;, 
including others involving faculty from NPRE.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2016 21:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://arfc.github.io/jekyll/update/2016/06/14/neup-demand-driven/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://arfc.github.io/jekyll/update/2016/06/14/neup-demand-driven/</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Huff Plans to Join NPRE</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am thrilled to be joining the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign as 
an Assistant Professor in the Department of Nuclear, Plasma and Radiological 
Engineering. I was honored to have been awarded a Blue Waters Assistant 
Professorship as well as an affiliate faculty appointment with the National 
Center for Supercomputing Applications. The support of NCSA is very meaningful 
to me and I hope to make important use of the high performance computing 
resources on campus when I arrive.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will begin my appointment on August 16, 2016. Until then, I’ll be wrapping up 
my work at the University of California, Berkeley. In addition, I’ll be 
preparing my first NPRE course, seeking graduate students and postdocs for a 
research group, finding a home in the Urbana-Champaign area, and setting up 
this website.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2016 20:03:54 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://arfc.github.io/jekyll/update/2016/02/06/huff-joins-npre/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://arfc.github.io/jekyll/update/2016/02/06/huff-joins-npre/</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
